Body Piercing, Kinky Sex, Dismemberment. The Things That Made Shakespeare Great
Tromeo & Juliet is a comedy, drama, romance film directed by Lloyd Kaufman.
All the body-piercing, kinky sex, and car crashes
that Shakespeare wanted but never had!
Join Tromeo and Juliet as they travel through Manhattan's underground in
search of climactic love, violence and the American Way.
Juliet Capulet, played by Jane Jensen.
Tromeo Que, played by Will Keenan.
Murray Martini, played by Valentine Miele.
Cappy Capulet, played by William Beckwith.
London Arbuckle, played by Steve Gibbons.
Sammy Capulet, played by Sean Gunn.
Tromeo and Juliet is a 1996 American independent transgressive romantic black comedy film and a loose
adaptation of the play Romeo and Juliet by William Shakespeare from Troma Entertainment.
The film was directed by Lloyd Kaufman from a screenplay he co-wrote
with James Gunn, who also served as associate director.
The film is a loose adaptation of the play, as it includes the extreme amounts of
sexuality and violence characteristic of Troma, as well as a revised ending.
The film's title is a blend of "Troma" and "Romeo and Juliet".
The tone is dark and lighthearted and emotional.